question_data = [
                     {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                      "question": "The first Maxis game to feature the fictional language &quot;Simlish&quot; was The Sims (2000).",
                      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                     {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                      "question": "TF2: The Heavy&#039;s voice actor, Gary Schwartz, voices the Demoman as well ",
                      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                     {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                      "question": "In the game &quot;Subnautica&quot;, a &quot;Cave Crawler&quot; will attack you.",
                      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                     {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                      "question": "David Baszucki was a co-founder of ROBLOX Corporation.", "correct_answer": "True",
                      "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                     {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                      "question": "In the video game &quot;Transistor&quot;, &quot;Red&quot; is the name of the main character.",
                      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                     {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                      "question": "Resident Evil 4 was originally meant to be a Nintendo GameCube exclusive.",
                      "correct_answer": "True",
                      "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                     {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                      "question": "In Portal, the Companion Cube&#039;s ARE sentient.", "correct_answer": "True",
                      "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                     {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                      "question": "The ADAM collecters in the Bioshock series are known as Little Sisters.",
                      "correct_answer": "True",
                      "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                     {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                      "question": "&quot;Return to Castle Wolfenstein&quot; was the only game of the Wolfenstein series where you don&#039;t play as William &quot;B.J.&quot; Blazkowicz.",
                      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                     {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                      "question": "In &quot;Resident Evil&quot;, only Chris has access to the grenade launcher.",
                      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]
